Picture yourself in a boat on a river With tangerine trees and marmalade skies
Somebody calls you, you answer quite slowly A girl with kaleidoscopes eyes
Cellophane flowers of yellow and green Towering over your head
Look for the girl with the sun in her eyes and she's gone
Lucy in the sky with diamonds
Pull her down to a bridge by a fountain Where rocking horse people eat marshmallow pies
Everyone smiles as you drift past the flowers That grow so incredibly high
Newspaper taxis appear on the shore Waiting to take you away
Hang in the back with your head in the clouds and you're gone
Lucy in the sky with diamonds
Picture yourself on a train in a station With plasticine porters with looking glass ties
Suddenly someone is there at the turnstile The girl with kaleidoscopes eyes
Lucy in the sky with diamonds